[
  {
    "questionText": "leave behind",
    "firstOption": "vandal",
    "secondOption": "harmony",
    "thirdOption": "abandon",
    "fourthOption": "baffle",
    "correctOption": "abandon",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sharp , intense , eager",
    "firstOption": "keen",
    "secondOption": "refer",
    "thirdOption": "recent",
    "fourthOption": "merit",
    "correctOption": "keen",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "resentful of anothers possessions or success",
    "firstOption": "jealous",
    "secondOption": "surplus",
    "thirdOption": "reform",
    "fourthOption": "spouse",
    "correctOption": "jealous",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ability to say right thing",
    "firstOption": "vast",
    "secondOption": "tact",
    "thirdOption": "alter",
    "fourthOption": "wail",
    "correctOption": "tact",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "blasphemous use of sacred words to express strong feelings",
    "firstOption": "cease",
    "secondOption": "doubt",
    "thirdOption": "unite",
    "fourthOption": "oath",
    "correctOption": "oath",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "empty , unoccupied",
    "firstOption": "recent",
    "secondOption": "vaccinate",
    "thirdOption": "vacant",
    "fourthOption": "tyrant",
    "correctOption": "vacant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "difficulty",
    "firstOption": "vacant",
    "secondOption": "data",
    "thirdOption": "gallant",
    "fourthOption": "hardship",
    "correctOption": "hardship",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "brave",
    "firstOption": "calculate",
    "secondOption": "recent",
    "thirdOption": "gallant",
    "fourthOption": "casual",
    "correctOption": "gallant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "information",
    "firstOption": "bait",
    "secondOption": "aware",
    "thirdOption": "flee",
    "fourthOption": "data",
    "correctOption": "data",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unusual",
    "firstOption": "masculine",
    "secondOption": "justice",
    "thirdOption": "unaccustomed",
    "fourthOption": "jagged",
    "correctOption": "unaccustomed",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a man who has not married",
    "firstOption": "censor",
    "secondOption": "bachelor",
    "thirdOption": "mythology",
    "fourthOption": "valor",
    "correctOption": "bachelor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "become fit , add a modifier to constituent",
    "firstOption": "charity",
    "secondOption": "squander",
    "thirdOption": "quarter",
    "fourthOption": "qualify",
    "correctOption": "qualify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a dread body",
    "firstOption": "corpse",
    "secondOption": "expose",
    "thirdOption": "probe",
    "fourthOption": "abuse",
    "correctOption": "corpse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hide",
    "firstOption": "conceal",
    "secondOption": "commend",
    "thirdOption": "soar",
    "fourthOption": "commence",
    "correctOption": "conceal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dark and depressing",
    "firstOption": "dismal",
    "secondOption": "vital",
    "thirdOption": "idol",
    "fourthOption": "final",
    "correctOption": "dismal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very cold",
    "firstOption": "frigid",
    "secondOption": "wrath",
    "thirdOption": "revive",
    "fourthOption": "vein",
    "correctOption": "frigid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "live in",
    "firstOption": "panic",
    "secondOption": "inhabit",
    "thirdOption": "forbid",
    "fourthOption": "vast",
    "correctOption": "inhabit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "without the power of feeling",
    "firstOption": "idle",
    "secondOption": "wasp",
    "thirdOption": "humid",
    "fourthOption": "numb",
    "correctOption": "numb",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "danger",
    "firstOption": "peril",
    "secondOption": "pierce",
    "thirdOption": "heir",
    "fourthOption": "pursue",
    "correctOption": "peril",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lie down",
    "firstOption": "recline",
    "secondOption": "masculine",
    "thirdOption": "beckon",
    "fourthOption": "vermin",
    "correctOption": "recline",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "scream",
    "firstOption": "verse",
    "secondOption": "shriek",
    "thirdOption": "budget",
    "fourthOption": "hasty",
    "correctOption": "shriek",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "evil",
    "firstOption": "sinister",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "visible",
    "fourthOption": "ignite",
    "correctOption": "sinister",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "allure",
    "firstOption": "opt",
    "secondOption": "tact",
    "thirdOption": "tempt",
    "fourthOption": "tumult",
    "correctOption": "tempt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bet",
    "firstOption": "harsh",
    "secondOption": "warden",
    "thirdOption": "tragedy",
    "fourthOption": "wager",
    "correctOption": "wager",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "usual",
    "firstOption": "vertical",
    "secondOption": "duplicate",
    "thirdOption": "typical",
    "fourthOption": "tyrant",
    "correctOption": "typical",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the lowest amount",
    "firstOption": "unify",
    "secondOption": "unite",
    "thirdOption": "minimum",
    "fourthOption": "monarch",
    "correctOption": "minimum",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hard to get",
    "firstOption": "scarce",
    "secondOption": "fierce",
    "thirdOption": "evade",
    "fourthOption": "glance",
    "correctOption": "scarce",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "once a year",
    "firstOption": "abandon",
    "secondOption": "annual",
    "thirdOption": "abuse",
    "fourthOption": "century",
    "correctOption": "annual",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make willing",
    "firstOption": "provide",
    "secondOption": "persuade",
    "thirdOption": "penalize",
    "fourthOption": "proceed",
    "correctOption": "persuade",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "necessary",
    "firstOption": "pension",
    "secondOption": "excessive",
    "thirdOption": "slender",
    "fourthOption": "essential",
    "correctOption": "essential",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a mixture",
    "firstOption": "burden",
    "secondOption": "glance",
    "thirdOption": "scald",
    "fourthOption": "blend",
    "correctOption": "blend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "able to be seen",
    "firstOption": "visible",
    "secondOption": "vessel",
    "thirdOption": "possible",
    "fourthOption": "dismal",
    "correctOption": "visible",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "costly",
    "firstOption": "expensive",
    "secondOption": "spouse",
    "thirdOption": "peril",
    "fourthOption": "awesome",
    "correctOption": "expensive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "natural ability",
    "firstOption": "gallant",
    "secondOption": "legend",
    "thirdOption": "tragedy",
    "fourthOption": "talent",
    "correctOption": "talent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "plan",
    "firstOption": "devour",
    "secondOption": "deceive",
    "thirdOption": "revive",
    "fourthOption": "devise",
    "correctOption": "devise",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a large quantity",
    "firstOption": "wholesale",
    "secondOption": "illegal",
    "thirdOption": "pledge",
    "fourthOption": "elevate",
    "correctOption": "wholesale",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fog",
    "firstOption": "prior",
    "secondOption": "valor",
    "thirdOption": "vapor",
    "fourthOption": "wail",
    "correctOption": "vapor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a very wicked person",
    "firstOption": "vain",
    "secondOption": "maintain",
    "thirdOption": "villain",
    "fourthOption": "violent",
    "correctOption": "villain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remove",
    "firstOption": "vicinity",
    "secondOption": "flexible",
    "thirdOption": "calamity",
    "fourthOption": "eliminate",
    "correctOption": "eliminate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "compact",
    "firstOption": "rage",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "devour",
    "fourthOption": "rash",
    "correctOption": "dense",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make use of",
    "firstOption": "pollute",
    "secondOption": "utilize",
    "thirdOption": "despite",
    "fourthOption": "fugitive",
    "correctOption": "utilize",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "moist",
    "firstOption": "mumble",
    "secondOption": "vein",
    "thirdOption": "vermin",
    "fourthOption": "humid",
    "correctOption": "humid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "explanation based on thought",
    "firstOption": "theory",
    "secondOption": "thrifty",
    "thirdOption": "hasty",
    "fourthOption": "wary",
    "correctOption": "theory",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go down",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "descend",
    "thirdOption": "discard",
    "fourthOption": "heed",
    "correctOption": "descend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go around",
    "firstOption": "masculine",
    "secondOption": "circulate",
    "thirdOption": "capsule",
    "fourthOption": "adequate",
    "correctOption": "circulate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "huge",
    "firstOption": "vicious",
    "secondOption": "promote",
    "thirdOption": "endure",
    "fourthOption": "enormous",
    "correctOption": "enormous",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tell beforehand",
    "firstOption": "prompt",
    "secondOption": "predict",
    "thirdOption": "resume",
    "fourthOption": "pierce",
    "correctOption": "predict",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disappear",
    "firstOption": "cinema",
    "secondOption": "devise",
    "thirdOption": "abolish",
    "fourthOption": "vanish",
    "correctOption": "vanish",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "beliefs handed down from one generation or another",
    "firstOption": "crafty",
    "secondOption": "rage",
    "thirdOption": "obtain",
    "fourthOption": "tradition",
    "correctOption": "tradition",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "in the country",
    "firstOption": "rural",
    "secondOption": "abroad",
    "thirdOption": "peril",
    "fourthOption": "brutal",
    "correctOption": "rural",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a load",
    "firstOption": "heed",
    "secondOption": "burden",
    "thirdOption": "plea",
    "fourthOption": "aware",
    "correctOption": "burden",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grounds of university",
    "firstOption": "jealous",
    "secondOption": "wail",
    "thirdOption": "opt",
    "fourthOption": "campus",
    "correctOption": "campus",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the large number",
    "firstOption": "authority",
    "secondOption": "calamity",
    "thirdOption": "majority",
    "fourthOption": "culprit",
    "correctOption": "majority",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bring together",
    "firstOption": "feeble",
    "secondOption": "assemble",
    "thirdOption": "famine",
    "fourthOption": "rarely",
    "correctOption": "assemble",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "travel to unknown regions",
    "firstOption": "collide",
    "secondOption": "valor",
    "thirdOption": "exhibit",
    "fourthOption": "explore",
    "correctOption": "explore",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "subject that people think",
    "firstOption": "compel",
    "secondOption": "oath",
    "thirdOption": "vapor",
    "fourthOption": "topic",
    "correctOption": "topic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a discussion against something",
    "firstOption": "defraud",
    "secondOption": "debate",
    "thirdOption": "revise",
    "fourthOption": "migrate",
    "correctOption": "debate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "get away from by cleverness",
    "firstOption": "evade",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "revive",
    "fourthOption": "decade",
    "correctOption": "evade",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "search into",
    "firstOption": "rage",
    "secondOption": "perish",
    "thirdOption": "prior",
    "fourthOption": "probe",
    "correctOption": "probe",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make better",
    "firstOption": "debate",
    "secondOption": "recede",
    "thirdOption": "reform",
    "fourthOption": "weird",
    "correctOption": "reform",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "come near",
    "firstOption": "popular",
    "secondOption": "appeal",
    "thirdOption": "approach",
    "fourthOption": "topic",
    "correctOption": "approach",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "discover",
    "firstOption": "reveal",
    "secondOption": "extract",
    "thirdOption": "detect",
    "fourthOption": "client",
    "correctOption": "detect",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fault",
    "firstOption": "exempt",
    "secondOption": "resist",
    "thirdOption": "defect",
    "fourthOption": "rave",
    "correctOption": "defect",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a person who work for pay",
    "firstOption": "excel",
    "secondOption": "employee",
    "thirdOption": "penalize",
    "fourthOption": "recline",
    "correctOption": "employee",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "give too little care",
    "firstOption": "tact",
    "secondOption": "plea",
    "thirdOption": "defect",
    "fourthOption": "neglect",
    "correctOption": "neglect",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "mislead",
    "firstOption": "deceive",
    "secondOption": "deprive",
    "thirdOption": "excessive",
    "fourthOption": "decrease",
    "correctOption": "deceive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "certainly",
    "firstOption": "unaccustomed",
    "secondOption": "adequate",
    "thirdOption": "undoubtedly",
    "fourthOption": "solitary",
    "correctOption": "undoubtedly",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "liked by most people",
    "firstOption": "opt",
    "secondOption": "ponder",
    "thirdOption": "popular",
    "fourthOption": "bulky",
    "correctOption": "popular",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "complete",
    "firstOption": "popular",
    "secondOption": "ponder",
    "thirdOption": "solitary",
    "fourthOption": "thorough",
    "correctOption": "thorough",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "customer",
    "firstOption": "defiant",
    "secondOption": "bait",
    "thirdOption": "client",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "client",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "completely",
    "firstOption": "comprehensive",
    "secondOption": "excessive",
    "thirdOption": "captive",
    "fourthOption": "consider",
    "correctOption": "comprehensive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "take something by cheating",
    "firstOption": "menace",
    "secondOption": "defraud",
    "thirdOption": "scald",
    "fourthOption": "weird",
    "correctOption": "defraud",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "delay",
    "firstOption": "postpone",
    "secondOption": "famine",
    "thirdOption": "respond",
    "fourthOption": "conclude",
    "correctOption": "postpone",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "agreement",
    "firstOption": "blend",
    "secondOption": "detect",
    "thirdOption": "urgent",
    "fourthOption": "consent",
    "correctOption": "consent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bulky",
    "firstOption": "unite",
    "secondOption": "massive",
    "thirdOption": "dispute",
    "fourthOption": "guide",
    "correctOption": "massive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a small case",
    "firstOption": "circulate",
    "secondOption": "appeal",
    "thirdOption": "confine",
    "fourthOption": "capsule",
    "correctOption": "capsule",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "protect",
    "firstOption": "pauper",
    "secondOption": "sneer",
    "thirdOption": "peril",
    "fourthOption": "preserve",
    "correctOption": "preserve",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "express strong disapproval",
    "firstOption": "denounce",
    "secondOption": "debate",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "source",
    "correctOption": "denounce",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having no like",
    "firstOption": "uneasy",
    "secondOption": "linger",
    "thirdOption": "unique",
    "fourthOption": "nimble",
    "correctOption": "unique",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "flood",
    "firstOption": "variety",
    "secondOption": "torrent",
    "thirdOption": "dread",
    "fourthOption": "frequent",
    "correctOption": "torrent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "feel injured angered at something",
    "firstOption": "frequent",
    "secondOption": "resent",
    "thirdOption": "blend",
    "fourthOption": "vein",
    "correctOption": "resent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disturb",
    "firstOption": "mortal",
    "secondOption": "molest",
    "thirdOption": "consent",
    "fourthOption": "mourn",
    "correctOption": "molest",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dark",
    "firstOption": "gloomy",
    "secondOption": "alter",
    "thirdOption": "roam",
    "fourthOption": "envy",
    "correctOption": "gloomy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unexpected",
    "firstOption": "respond",
    "secondOption": "unique",
    "thirdOption": "pursue",
    "fourthOption": "unforeseen",
    "correctOption": "unforeseen",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "overstate",
    "firstOption": "decrease",
    "secondOption": "eliminate",
    "thirdOption": "estimate",
    "fourthOption": "exaggerate",
    "correctOption": "exaggerate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "non professional",
    "firstOption": "hinder",
    "secondOption": "heir",
    "thirdOption": "refer",
    "fourthOption": "amateur",
    "correctOption": "amateur",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "average",
    "firstOption": "explore",
    "secondOption": "mediocre",
    "thirdOption": "relieve",
    "fourthOption": "refer",
    "correctOption": "mediocre",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lack of sameness",
    "firstOption": "valiant",
    "secondOption": "peril",
    "thirdOption": "variety",
    "fourthOption": "vain",
    "correctOption": "variety",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "true",
    "firstOption": "daze",
    "secondOption": "oral",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "vain",
    "correctOption": "valid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "live longer than",
    "firstOption": "survive",
    "secondOption": "revive",
    "thirdOption": "shrill",
    "fourthOption": "massive",
    "correctOption": "survive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "mysterious",
    "firstOption": "depict",
    "secondOption": "perish",
    "thirdOption": "weird",
    "fourthOption": "recede",
    "correctOption": "weird",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "important",
    "firstOption": "violent",
    "secondOption": "homicide",
    "thirdOption": "opponent",
    "fourthOption": "prominent",
    "correctOption": "prominent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "care",
    "firstOption": "depart",
    "secondOption": "merit",
    "thirdOption": "security",
    "fourthOption": "severity",
    "correctOption": "security",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "large",
    "firstOption": "budget",
    "secondOption": "flee",
    "thirdOption": "bulky",
    "fourthOption": "verify",
    "correctOption": "bulky",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unwilling",
    "firstOption": "reluctant",
    "secondOption": "expand",
    "thirdOption": "loyalty",
    "fourthOption": "delinquent",
    "correctOption": "reluctant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "plain",
    "firstOption": "obvious",
    "secondOption": "prior",
    "thirdOption": "morgue",
    "fourthOption": "fiction",
    "correctOption": "obvious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "neighborhood",
    "firstOption": "vicinity",
    "secondOption": "crafty",
    "thirdOption": "cancel",
    "fourthOption": "obesity",
    "correctOption": "vicinity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "100 years",
    "firstOption": "menace",
    "secondOption": "verify",
    "thirdOption": "clergy",
    "fourthOption": "century",
    "correctOption": "century",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "violent anger",
    "firstOption": "rage",
    "secondOption": "rash",
    "thirdOption": "daze",
    "fourthOption": "probe",
    "correctOption": "rage",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "paper which provides information or evidence",
    "firstOption": "torment",
    "secondOption": "mount",
    "thirdOption": "document",
    "fourthOption": "occupant",
    "correctOption": "document",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "finish",
    "firstOption": "unique",
    "secondOption": "conclude",
    "thirdOption": "confine",
    "fourthOption": "relieve",
    "correctOption": "conclude",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not to be deny",
    "firstOption": "undeniable",
    "secondOption": "essential",
    "thirdOption": "adequate",
    "fourthOption": "unstable",
    "correctOption": "undeniable",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "oppose",
    "firstOption": "redeem",
    "secondOption": "molest",
    "thirdOption": "justice",
    "fourthOption": "resist",
    "correctOption": "resist",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "have not enough",
    "firstOption": "wad",
    "secondOption": "gleam",
    "thirdOption": "tact",
    "fourthOption": "lack",
    "correctOption": "lack",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disregard",
    "firstOption": "ingenious",
    "secondOption": "soar",
    "thirdOption": "mature",
    "fourthOption": "ignore",
    "correctOption": "ignore",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "call to flight",
    "firstOption": "harsh",
    "secondOption": "confine",
    "thirdOption": "threat",
    "fourthOption": "challenge",
    "correctOption": "challenge",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "small scale",
    "firstOption": "migrate",
    "secondOption": "innovative",
    "thirdOption": "miniature",
    "fourthOption": "vicious",
    "correctOption": "miniature",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "reveal the origin of something",
    "firstOption": "rural",
    "secondOption": "denounce",
    "thirdOption": "source",
    "fourthOption": "blunder",
    "correctOption": "source",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "do better than",
    "firstOption": "cancel",
    "secondOption": "wager",
    "thirdOption": "excel",
    "fourthOption": "morsel",
    "correctOption": "excel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "of women or girl",
    "firstOption": "recline",
    "secondOption": "feminine",
    "thirdOption": "nominate",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "feminine",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "get up on",
    "firstOption": "abuse",
    "secondOption": "summit",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "expand",
    "correctOption": "mount",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be a rival",
    "firstOption": "commend",
    "secondOption": "tempest",
    "thirdOption": "promote",
    "fourthOption": "compete",
    "correctOption": "compete",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "causing great fear",
    "firstOption": "idle",
    "secondOption": "wad",
    "thirdOption": "detest",
    "fourthOption": "dread",
    "correctOption": "dread",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "male",
    "firstOption": "scald",
    "secondOption": "manipulate",
    "thirdOption": "masculine",
    "fourthOption": "pacify",
    "correctOption": "masculine",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "threat",
    "firstOption": "penalize",
    "secondOption": "menace",
    "thirdOption": "commence",
    "fourthOption": "defect",
    "correctOption": "menace",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "leaning",
    "firstOption": "tendency",
    "secondOption": "evidence",
    "thirdOption": "resent",
    "fourthOption": "consent",
    "correctOption": "tendency",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "set to low a value",
    "firstOption": "adequate",
    "secondOption": "negative",
    "thirdOption": "decade",
    "fourthOption": "underestimate",
    "correctOption": "underestimate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having won victory",
    "firstOption": "debtor",
    "secondOption": "victorious",
    "thirdOption": "consent",
    "fourthOption": "compare",
    "correctOption": "victorious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "several",
    "firstOption": "juvenile",
    "secondOption": "numerous",
    "thirdOption": "theory",
    "fourthOption": "perish",
    "correctOption": "numerous",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "easily bent",
    "firstOption": "undeniable",
    "secondOption": "flexible",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "peril",
    "correctOption": "flexible",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "that which makes clear the truth",
    "firstOption": "evidence",
    "secondOption": "finance",
    "thirdOption": "denounce",
    "fourthOption": "pierce",
    "correctOption": "evidence",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "alone",
    "firstOption": "solitary",
    "secondOption": "uneasy",
    "thirdOption": "oral",
    "fourthOption": "nominate",
    "correctOption": "solitary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "power of seeing",
    "firstOption": "beckon",
    "secondOption": "vision",
    "thirdOption": "respond",
    "fourthOption": "resign",
    "correctOption": "vision",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "happening often",
    "firstOption": "event",
    "secondOption": "frequent",
    "thirdOption": "respond",
    "fourthOption": "urgent",
    "correctOption": "frequent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quick view",
    "firstOption": "pierce",
    "secondOption": "glimpse",
    "thirdOption": "campus",
    "fourthOption": "spouse",
    "correctOption": "glimpse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "done not long ago",
    "firstOption": "recent",
    "secondOption": "consent",
    "thirdOption": "excel",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "recent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ten years",
    "firstOption": "decade",
    "secondOption": "devour",
    "thirdOption": "detect",
    "fourthOption": "wager",
    "correctOption": "decade",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fail to act quickly",
    "firstOption": "temperate",
    "secondOption": "defiant",
    "thirdOption": "elevate",
    "fourthOption": "hesitate",
    "correctOption": "hesitate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "foolish",
    "firstOption": "depart",
    "secondOption": "absurd",
    "thirdOption": "annual",
    "fourthOption": "abundant",
    "correctOption": "absurd",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disagreement",
    "firstOption": "insist",
    "secondOption": "compete",
    "thirdOption": "conflict",
    "fourthOption": "panic",
    "correctOption": "conflict",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "less than half",
    "firstOption": "morgue",
    "secondOption": "unruly",
    "thirdOption": "minority",
    "fourthOption": "misfortune",
    "correctOption": "minority",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "that which is imagined",
    "firstOption": "partial",
    "secondOption": "villain",
    "thirdOption": "vision",
    "fourthOption": "fiction",
    "correctOption": "fiction",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "set on fire",
    "firstOption": "vicinity",
    "secondOption": "abide",
    "thirdOption": "idle",
    "fourthOption": "ignite",
    "correctOption": "ignite",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "put an end to",
    "firstOption": "avoid",
    "secondOption": "resist",
    "thirdOption": "abolish",
    "fourthOption": "majority",
    "correctOption": "abolish",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having to do with cities",
    "firstOption": "budget",
    "secondOption": "legend",
    "thirdOption": "numb",
    "fourthOption": "urban",
    "correctOption": "urban",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "people of the city or country",
    "firstOption": "retain",
    "secondOption": "nourish",
    "thirdOption": "panic",
    "fourthOption": "population",
    "correctOption": "population",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "free in expressing",
    "firstOption": "rave",
    "secondOption": "mount",
    "thirdOption": "frank",
    "fourthOption": "vein",
    "correctOption": "frank",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make dirty",
    "firstOption": "pollute",
    "secondOption": "talent",
    "thirdOption": "possible",
    "fourthOption": "promote",
    "correctOption": "pollute",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make known",
    "firstOption": "refer",
    "secondOption": "final",
    "thirdOption": "reveal",
    "fourthOption": "recent",
    "correctOption": "reveal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "forbid by law",
    "firstOption": "prohibit",
    "secondOption": "resign",
    "thirdOption": "abolish",
    "fourthOption": "partial",
    "correctOption": "prohibit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "immediate",
    "firstOption": "parole",
    "secondOption": "prohibit",
    "thirdOption": "resign",
    "fourthOption": "urgent",
    "correctOption": "urgent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "as much as is needed",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "adequate",
    "thirdOption": "persuade",
    "fourthOption": "data",
    "correctOption": "adequate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "become less",
    "firstOption": "decrease",
    "secondOption": "recede",
    "thirdOption": "dread",
    "fourthOption": "emerge",
    "correctOption": "decrease",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "able to be heard",
    "firstOption": "audible",
    "secondOption": "survive",
    "thirdOption": "assemble",
    "fourthOption": "possible",
    "correctOption": "audible",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "writer for newspaper",
    "firstOption": "harvast",
    "secondOption": "logical",
    "thirdOption": "potential",
    "fourthOption": "journalist",
    "correctOption": "journalist",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "starvation",
    "firstOption": "famine",
    "secondOption": "fierce",
    "thirdOption": "feminine",
    "fourthOption": "parole",
    "correctOption": "famine",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "come back to life",
    "firstOption": "ignite",
    "secondOption": "negative",
    "thirdOption": "revive",
    "fourthOption": "resume",
    "correctOption": "revive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "start",
    "firstOption": "commend",
    "secondOption": "evidence",
    "thirdOption": "confine",
    "fourthOption": "commence",
    "correctOption": "commence",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "watchful",
    "firstOption": "masculine",
    "secondOption": "observant",
    "thirdOption": "baggage",
    "fourthOption": "verdict",
    "correctOption": "observant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "recognize as being",
    "firstOption": "deceive",
    "secondOption": "adequate",
    "thirdOption": "debtor",
    "fourthOption": "identify",
    "correctOption": "identify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "move from one place to another",
    "firstOption": "migrate",
    "secondOption": "menace",
    "thirdOption": "charity",
    "fourthOption": "adequate",
    "correctOption": "migrate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a ship",
    "firstOption": "resist",
    "secondOption": "vessel",
    "thirdOption": "kneel",
    "fourthOption": "excel",
    "correctOption": "vessel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "continue firmly",
    "firstOption": "persuade",
    "secondOption": "persist",
    "thirdOption": "detest",
    "fourthOption": "vermin",
    "correctOption": "persist",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "misty",
    "firstOption": "unify",
    "secondOption": "oral",
    "thirdOption": "hazy",
    "fourthOption": "wrath",
    "correctOption": "hazy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a flash",
    "firstOption": "illegal",
    "secondOption": "gleam",
    "thirdOption": "swarm",
    "fourthOption": "gloomy",
    "correctOption": "gleam",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who prepare publication",
    "firstOption": "utter",
    "secondOption": "prior",
    "thirdOption": "editor",
    "fourthOption": "valor",
    "correctOption": "editor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lawless",
    "firstOption": "annual",
    "secondOption": "mortal",
    "thirdOption": "clergy",
    "fourthOption": "unruly",
    "correctOption": "unruly",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "opponent",
    "firstOption": "rival",
    "secondOption": "shrill",
    "thirdOption": "dismal",
    "fourthOption": "idol",
    "correctOption": "rival",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "rough force",
    "firstOption": "valiant",
    "secondOption": "idle",
    "thirdOption": "violent",
    "fourthOption": "talent",
    "correctOption": "violent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cruel",
    "firstOption": "brutal",
    "secondOption": "outlaw",
    "thirdOption": "vital",
    "fourthOption": "casual",
    "correctOption": "brutal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "rival",
    "firstOption": "opponent",
    "secondOption": "torment",
    "thirdOption": "expose",
    "fourthOption": "prompt",
    "correctOption": "opponent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a noisy fight",
    "firstOption": "fragile",
    "secondOption": "probe",
    "thirdOption": "rage",
    "fourthOption": "brawl",
    "correctOption": "brawl",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "an exact copy",
    "firstOption": "placard",
    "secondOption": "duplicate",
    "thirdOption": "debate",
    "fourthOption": "precede",
    "correctOption": "duplicate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "evil",
    "firstOption": "vague",
    "secondOption": "vicious",
    "thirdOption": "diminish",
    "fourthOption": "spouse",
    "correctOption": "vicious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "turn around",
    "firstOption": "whirling",
    "secondOption": "harmony",
    "thirdOption": "mourn",
    "fourthOption": "vermin",
    "correctOption": "whirling",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "one who is expected",
    "firstOption": "underdog",
    "secondOption": "kneel",
    "thirdOption": "hinder",
    "fourthOption": "miserly",
    "correctOption": "underdog",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "push with force",
    "firstOption": "detest",
    "secondOption": "tact",
    "thirdOption": "thrust",
    "fourthOption": "tempt",
    "correctOption": "thrust",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "confused completely",
    "firstOption": "blunder",
    "secondOption": "bewildered",
    "thirdOption": "dwindle",
    "fourthOption": "evidence",
    "correctOption": "bewildered",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "enlarge",
    "firstOption": "frank",
    "secondOption": "vacant",
    "thirdOption": "expand",
    "fourthOption": "event",
    "correctOption": "expand",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "change",
    "firstOption": "quote",
    "secondOption": "alter",
    "thirdOption": "linger",
    "fourthOption": "oath",
    "correctOption": "alter",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fully grown",
    "firstOption": "mature",
    "secondOption": "oath",
    "thirdOption": "mourn",
    "fourthOption": "endure",
    "correctOption": "mature",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "holy",
    "firstOption": "valid",
    "secondOption": "sacred",
    "thirdOption": "proceed",
    "fourthOption": "jagged",
    "correctOption": "sacred",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "change",
    "firstOption": "devise",
    "secondOption": "recede",
    "thirdOption": "verse",
    "fourthOption": "revise",
    "correctOption": "revise",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "promise",
    "firstOption": "flee",
    "secondOption": "plea",
    "thirdOption": "pledge",
    "fourthOption": "idle",
    "correctOption": "pledge",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "happening by chance",
    "firstOption": "dismal",
    "secondOption": "partial",
    "thirdOption": "mature",
    "fourthOption": "casual",
    "correctOption": "casual",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "follow",
    "firstOption": "harsh",
    "secondOption": "surplus",
    "thirdOption": "pursue",
    "fourthOption": "pledge",
    "correctOption": "pursue",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "in complete agreement",
    "firstOption": "unanimous",
    "secondOption": "obvious",
    "thirdOption": "contagious",
    "fourthOption": "unite",
    "correctOption": "unanimous",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lucky",
    "firstOption": "corpse",
    "secondOption": "misfortune",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "fortunate",
    "correctOption": "fortunate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "one who goes first",
    "firstOption": "violent",
    "secondOption": "quarter",
    "thirdOption": "pioneer",
    "fourthOption": "employee",
    "correctOption": "pioneer",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fresh",
    "firstOption": "innovative",
    "secondOption": "ignite",
    "thirdOption": "survive",
    "fourthOption": "justice",
    "correctOption": "innovative",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "slim",
    "firstOption": "plea",
    "secondOption": "slender",
    "thirdOption": "pledge",
    "fourthOption": "alter",
    "correctOption": "slender",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "excel",
    "firstOption": "swarm",
    "secondOption": "pursue",
    "thirdOption": "surpass",
    "fourthOption": "rash",
    "correctOption": "surpass",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very great",
    "firstOption": "harvest",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "valiant",
    "fourthOption": "tact",
    "correctOption": "vast",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not believe",
    "firstOption": "roam",
    "secondOption": "debate",
    "thirdOption": "doubt",
    "fourthOption": "numb",
    "correctOption": "doubt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "amount of space",
    "firstOption": "capacity",
    "secondOption": "captive",
    "thirdOption": "security",
    "fourthOption": "inhabit",
    "correctOption": "capacity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "get into",
    "firstOption": "encourage",
    "secondOption": "calculate",
    "thirdOption": "penetrate",
    "fourthOption": "adequate",
    "correctOption": "penetrate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go into",
    "firstOption": "idol",
    "secondOption": "pierce",
    "thirdOption": "evidence",
    "fourthOption": "preserve",
    "correctOption": "pierce",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "exactly right",
    "firstOption": "corpse",
    "secondOption": "adequate",
    "thirdOption": "accurate",
    "fourthOption": "migrate",
    "correctOption": "accurate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "optical instrument that magnifies images of objects invisible to the naked eye",
    "firstOption": "misfortune",
    "secondOption": "microscope",
    "thirdOption": "scorch",
    "fourthOption": "embrace",
    "correctOption": "microscope",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thankful",
    "firstOption": "novel",
    "secondOption": "wager",
    "thirdOption": "preserve",
    "fourthOption": "grateful",
    "correctOption": "grateful",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very careful",
    "firstOption": "attract",
    "secondOption": "vicious",
    "thirdOption": "contagious",
    "fourthOption": "cautious",
    "correctOption": "cautious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sure",
    "firstOption": "prohibit",
    "secondOption": "confident",
    "thirdOption": "homicide",
    "fourthOption": "slender",
    "correctOption": "confident",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "attraction",
    "firstOption": "pauper",
    "secondOption": "vital",
    "thirdOption": "appeal",
    "fourthOption": "compel",
    "correctOption": "appeal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "one who cannot break away from a habit",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "panic",
    "thirdOption": "addict",
    "fourthOption": "defiant",
    "correctOption": "addict",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cautious",
    "firstOption": "ban",
    "secondOption": "envy",
    "thirdOption": "wary",
    "fourthOption": "bait",
    "correctOption": "wary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "knowing",
    "firstOption": "maim",
    "secondOption": "aware",
    "thirdOption": "wrath",
    "fourthOption": "verse",
    "correctOption": "aware",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bad luck",
    "firstOption": "mortal",
    "secondOption": "misfortune",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "miniature",
    "correctOption": "misfortune",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "keep away from",
    "firstOption": "valid",
    "secondOption": "opt",
    "thirdOption": "heed",
    "fourthOption": "avoid",
    "correctOption": "avoid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "miserable",
    "firstOption": "wretched",
    "secondOption": "weird",
    "thirdOption": "dense",
    "fourthOption": "recede",
    "correctOption": "wretched",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "small barrel",
    "firstOption": "ban",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "snub",
    "fourthOption": "keg",
    "correctOption": "keg",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "feed",
    "firstOption": "burden",
    "secondOption": "nourish",
    "thirdOption": "charity",
    "fourthOption": "mourn",
    "correctOption": "nourish",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "rough to the touch",
    "firstOption": "harsh",
    "secondOption": "panic",
    "thirdOption": "oath",
    "fourthOption": "perish",
    "correctOption": "harsh",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "amount",
    "firstOption": "quota",
    "secondOption": "partial",
    "thirdOption": "quantity",
    "fourthOption": "signify",
    "correctOption": "quantity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "select",
    "firstOption": "toil",
    "secondOption": "oral",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "opt",
    "correctOption": "opt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a sad play",
    "firstOption": "tragedy",
    "secondOption": "untidy",
    "thirdOption": "qualify",
    "fourthOption": "daze",
    "correctOption": "tragedy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "walker",
    "firstOption": "penetrate",
    "secondOption": "penalize",
    "thirdOption": "pedestrian",
    "fourthOption": "severity",
    "correctOption": "pedestrian",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a quick look",
    "firstOption": "gleam",
    "secondOption": "vague",
    "thirdOption": "aware",
    "fourthOption": "glance",
    "correctOption": "glance",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "amount of money that can be spend",
    "firstOption": "budget",
    "secondOption": "addict",
    "thirdOption": "linger",
    "fourthOption": "blunder",
    "correctOption": "budget",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quick moving",
    "firstOption": "inhabit",
    "secondOption": "assemble",
    "thirdOption": "nimble",
    "fourthOption": "nominate",
    "correctOption": "nimble",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "handle skilfully",
    "firstOption": "manipulate",
    "secondOption": "pollute",
    "thirdOption": "unique",
    "fourthOption": "maximum",
    "correctOption": "manipulate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "careless",
    "firstOption": "reckless",
    "secondOption": "decrease",
    "thirdOption": "neglect",
    "fourthOption": "revive",
    "correctOption": "reckless",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "terrible",
    "firstOption": "avoid",
    "secondOption": "collide",
    "thirdOption": "horrid",
    "fourthOption": "vermin",
    "correctOption": "horrid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "talk widely",
    "firstOption": "rave",
    "secondOption": "wad",
    "thirdOption": "lack",
    "fourthOption": "reveal",
    "correctOption": "rave",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not wasting money or time",
    "firstOption": "cinema",
    "secondOption": "annual",
    "thirdOption": "conceal",
    "fourthOption": "economical",
    "correctOption": "economical",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grease",
    "firstOption": "threat",
    "secondOption": "vertical",
    "thirdOption": "lubricate",
    "fourthOption": "depict",
    "correctOption": "lubricate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clever",
    "firstOption": "contagious",
    "secondOption": "ingenious",
    "thirdOption": "numerous",
    "fourthOption": "ignore",
    "correctOption": "ingenious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "gathering in of grain",
    "firstOption": "harvest",
    "secondOption": "defect",
    "thirdOption": "thrust",
    "fourthOption": "event",
    "correctOption": "harvest",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "more than enough",
    "firstOption": "appoint",
    "secondOption": "annual",
    "thirdOption": "abundant",
    "fourthOption": "blunder",
    "correctOption": "abundant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "restless",
    "firstOption": "uneasy",
    "secondOption": "quota",
    "thirdOption": "sneer",
    "fourthOption": "unearth",
    "correctOption": "uneasy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "compute",
    "firstOption": "candidate",
    "secondOption": "elevate",
    "thirdOption": "calculate",
    "fourthOption": "manipulate",
    "correctOption": "calculate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "take in or suck up",
    "firstOption": "respond",
    "secondOption": "theory",
    "thirdOption": "jest",
    "fourthOption": "absorb",
    "correctOption": "absorb",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "from a judgment",
    "firstOption": "estimate",
    "secondOption": "anticipate",
    "thirdOption": "debate",
    "fourthOption": "summit",
    "correctOption": "estimate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a small bite",
    "firstOption": "forbid",
    "secondOption": "morsel",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "corpse",
    "correctOption": "morsel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "share of a total due from or to particular state",
    "firstOption": "quota",
    "secondOption": "vital",
    "thirdOption": "quench",
    "fourthOption": "oath",
    "correctOption": "quota",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sign or cause of possible evil or harm",
    "firstOption": "threat",
    "secondOption": "rural",
    "thirdOption": "defect",
    "fourthOption": "recent",
    "correctOption": "threat",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "prohibit",
    "firstOption": "blend",
    "secondOption": "envy",
    "thirdOption": "ban",
    "fourthOption": "opt",
    "correctOption": "ban",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unreasoning fear",
    "firstOption": "ban",
    "secondOption": "panic",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "peril",
    "correctOption": "panic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fit",
    "firstOption": "probe",
    "secondOption": "appropriate",
    "thirdOption": "prompt",
    "fourthOption": "encourage",
    "correctOption": "appropriate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "come out",
    "firstOption": "merit",
    "secondOption": "event",
    "thirdOption": "emerge",
    "fourthOption": "scarce",
    "correctOption": "emerge",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "with sharp points sticking out",
    "firstOption": "pacify",
    "secondOption": "jagged",
    "thirdOption": "budget",
    "fourthOption": "pauper",
    "correctOption": "jagged",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stay on",
    "firstOption": "vigor",
    "secondOption": "heir",
    "thirdOption": "linger",
    "fourthOption": "legend",
    "correctOption": "linger",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hide in order to make a surprise attack",
    "firstOption": "campus",
    "secondOption": "mute",
    "thirdOption": "ambush",
    "fourthOption": "abuse",
    "correctOption": "ambush",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "skilful deceiving others",
    "firstOption": "capacity",
    "secondOption": "rash",
    "thirdOption": "crafty",
    "fourthOption": "oath",
    "correctOption": "crafty",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "openly resisting",
    "firstOption": "feminine",
    "secondOption": "detest",
    "thirdOption": "vein",
    "fourthOption": "defiant",
    "correctOption": "defiant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "active strength or force",
    "firstOption": "weird",
    "secondOption": "editor",
    "thirdOption": "unify",
    "fourthOption": "vigor",
    "correctOption": "vigor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be destroyed",
    "firstOption": "corpse",
    "secondOption": "perish",
    "thirdOption": "probe",
    "fourthOption": "fertile",
    "correctOption": "perish",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "easy broken",
    "firstOption": "revive",
    "secondOption": "recede",
    "thirdOption": "fragile",
    "fourthOption": "revise",
    "correctOption": "fragile",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "prisoner",
    "firstOption": "captive",
    "secondOption": "valid",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "topic",
    "correctOption": "captive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be successful",
    "firstOption": "prosper",
    "secondOption": "pension",
    "thirdOption": "provide",
    "fourthOption": "pursue",
    "correctOption": "prosper",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be successful",
    "firstOption": "prosper",
    "secondOption": "pension",
    "thirdOption": "provide",
    "fourthOption": "pursue",
    "correctOption": "prosper",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "request",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "plea",
    "thirdOption": "mute",
    "fourthOption": "numb",
    "correctOption": "plea",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tired",
    "firstOption": "tact",
    "secondOption": "century",
    "thirdOption": "frank",
    "fourthOption": "weary",
    "correctOption": "weary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "come together with force",
    "firstOption": "collide",
    "secondOption": "forbid",
    "thirdOption": "guide",
    "fourthOption": "confirm",
    "correctOption": "collide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "verify",
    "firstOption": "conflict",
    "secondOption": "toil",
    "thirdOption": "confirm",
    "fourthOption": "ponder",
    "correctOption": "confirm",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "confirm",
    "firstOption": "gloomy",
    "secondOption": "peril",
    "thirdOption": "clergy",
    "fourthOption": "verify",
    "correctOption": "verify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "expect",
    "firstOption": "anticipate",
    "secondOption": "migrate",
    "thirdOption": "hesitate",
    "fourthOption": "lubricate",
    "correctOption": "anticipate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a difficult choice",
    "firstOption": "dread",
    "secondOption": "dilemma",
    "thirdOption": "disrupt",
    "fourthOption": "exempt",
    "correctOption": "dilemma",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a roundabout way",
    "firstOption": "depict",
    "secondOption": "obvious",
    "thirdOption": "detour",
    "fourthOption": "decade",
    "correctOption": "detour",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "goodness",
    "firstOption": "bait",
    "secondOption": "pierce",
    "thirdOption": "merit",
    "fourthOption": "depict",
    "correctOption": "merit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "send over",
    "firstOption": "transmit",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "calamity",
    "fourthOption": "rapid",
    "correctOption": "transmit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "release",
    "firstOption": "recede",
    "secondOption": "precede",
    "thirdOption": "relieve",
    "fourthOption": "resume",
    "correctOption": "relieve",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be to hard to understand",
    "firstOption": "cancel",
    "secondOption": "rave",
    "thirdOption": "baffle",
    "fourthOption": "shrill",
    "correctOption": "baffle",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "keeper",
    "firstOption": "warden",
    "secondOption": "swarm",
    "thirdOption": "thrust",
    "fourthOption": "wasp",
    "correctOption": "warden",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "admit to be true",
    "firstOption": "awkward",
    "secondOption": "acknowledge",
    "thirdOption": "parole",
    "fourthOption": "audible",
    "correctOption": "acknowledge",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fair dealing",
    "firstOption": "majestic",
    "secondOption": "justice",
    "thirdOption": "depict",
    "fourthOption": "unstable",
    "correctOption": "justice",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "an offender",
    "firstOption": "delinquent",
    "secondOption": "linger",
    "thirdOption": "consent",
    "fourthOption": "resent",
    "correctOption": "delinquent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "refuse to take",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "jest",
    "thirdOption": "resist",
    "fourthOption": "pierce",
    "correctOption": "reject",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "take away from force",
    "firstOption": "deprive",
    "secondOption": "depict",
    "thirdOption": "deceive",
    "fourthOption": "defraud",
    "correctOption": "deprive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "husband or wife",
    "firstOption": "vague",
    "secondOption": "scarce",
    "thirdOption": "spouse",
    "fourthOption": "doubt",
    "correctOption": "spouse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "occupation",
    "firstOption": "oath",
    "secondOption": "vocation",
    "thirdOption": "valiant",
    "fourthOption": "vicious",
    "correctOption": "vocation",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unsteady",
    "firstOption": "uneasy",
    "secondOption": "unanimous",
    "thirdOption": "undeniable",
    "fourthOption": "unstable",
    "correctOption": "unstable",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "murder",
    "firstOption": "forbid",
    "secondOption": "utilize",
    "thirdOption": "homicide",
    "fourthOption": "promote",
    "correctOption": "homicide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "set a penalty for",
    "firstOption": "expensive",
    "secondOption": "endure",
    "thirdOption": "reptile",
    "fourthOption": "penalize",
    "correctOption": "penalize",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "persons who receive benefit",
    "firstOption": "venture",
    "secondOption": "beneficiary",
    "thirdOption": "sneer",
    "fourthOption": "reluctant",
    "correctOption": "beneficiary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "any animal which creeps or crawls",
    "firstOption": "devise",
    "secondOption": "reptile",
    "thirdOption": "resent",
    "fourthOption": "peril",
    "correctOption": "reptile",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "seldom",
    "firstOption": "sacred",
    "secondOption": "rarely",
    "thirdOption": "rave",
    "fourthOption": "miserly",
    "correctOption": "rarely",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make a rule against",
    "firstOption": "obtain",
    "secondOption": "avoid",
    "thirdOption": "urban",
    "fourthOption": "forbid",
    "correctOption": "forbid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "reasonable",
    "firstOption": "lottery",
    "secondOption": "topic",
    "thirdOption": "logical",
    "fourthOption": "mortal",
    "correctOption": "logical",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "show",
    "firstOption": "audible",
    "secondOption": "expose",
    "thirdOption": "exhibit",
    "fourthOption": "insist",
    "correctOption": "exhibit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "move forward",
    "firstOption": "proceed",
    "secondOption": "discard",
    "thirdOption": "related",
    "fourthOption": "precede",
    "correctOption": "proceed",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "foresight",
    "firstOption": "precede",
    "secondOption": "precaution",
    "thirdOption": "penalize",
    "fourthOption": "vocation",
    "correctOption": "precaution",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "pull out",
    "firstOption": "extract",
    "secondOption": "betray",
    "thirdOption": "exhibit",
    "fourthOption": "detect",
    "correctOption": "extract",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "earlier",
    "firstOption": "deprive",
    "secondOption": "debtor",
    "thirdOption": "parole",
    "fourthOption": "prior",
    "correctOption": "prior",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a hug",
    "firstOption": "emerge",
    "secondOption": "embrace",
    "thirdOption": "mature",
    "fourthOption": "monarch",
    "correctOption": "embrace",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "brave",
    "firstOption": "urgent",
    "secondOption": "casual",
    "thirdOption": "valiant",
    "fourthOption": "valid",
    "correctOption": "valiant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not total",
    "firstOption": "partial",
    "secondOption": "vertical",
    "thirdOption": "prior",
    "fourthOption": "brutal",
    "correctOption": "partial",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "savage",
    "firstOption": "fierce",
    "secondOption": "scorch",
    "thirdOption": "famine",
    "fourthOption": "deceive",
    "correctOption": "fierce",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hate",
    "firstOption": "detest",
    "secondOption": "event",
    "thirdOption": "depict",
    "fourthOption": "betray",
    "correctOption": "detest",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "show scorn",
    "firstOption": "flee",
    "secondOption": "alter",
    "thirdOption": "hinder",
    "fourthOption": "sneer",
    "correctOption": "sneer",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "frown",
    "firstOption": "idol",
    "secondOption": "soar",
    "thirdOption": "spouse",
    "fourthOption": "scowl",
    "correctOption": "scowl",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "give courage to",
    "firstOption": "ignore",
    "secondOption": "collapse",
    "thirdOption": "menace",
    "fourthOption": "encourage",
    "correctOption": "encourage",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "think about to decide",
    "firstOption": "confident",
    "secondOption": "linger",
    "thirdOption": "consider",
    "fourthOption": "horrid",
    "correctOption": "consider",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "small harmful animals or insects that cause damage to crops and property",
    "firstOption": "wander",
    "secondOption": "rival",
    "thirdOption": "abroad",
    "fourthOption": "vermin",
    "correctOption": "vermin",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cry loudly",
    "firstOption": "heir",
    "secondOption": "toil",
    "thirdOption": "wail",
    "fourthOption": "plea",
    "correctOption": "wail",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "something that stands for or represents something else",
    "firstOption": "numb",
    "secondOption": "prior",
    "thirdOption": "symbol",
    "fourthOption": "wobble",
    "correctOption": "symbol",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "power delegated to another",
    "firstOption": "threat",
    "secondOption": "authority",
    "thirdOption": "corpse",
    "fourthOption": "trifle",
    "correctOption": "authority",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "on neither side of a quarrel",
    "firstOption": "extract",
    "secondOption": "refer",
    "thirdOption": "neutral",
    "fourthOption": "date",
    "correctOption": "neutral",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a small about",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "peril",
    "thirdOption": "flee",
    "fourthOption": "trifle",
    "correctOption": "trifle",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "creator",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "amateur",
    "thirdOption": "predict",
    "fourthOption": "architect",
    "correctOption": "architect",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "wedding ceremony",
    "firstOption": "maim",
    "secondOption": "magnify",
    "thirdOption": "traitor",
    "fourthOption": "matrimony",
    "correctOption": "matrimony",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "suitcases",
    "firstOption": "abide",
    "secondOption": "baggage",
    "thirdOption": "wager",
    "fourthOption": "vacant",
    "correctOption": "baggage",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "spend foolishly",
    "firstOption": "snub",
    "secondOption": "spouse",
    "thirdOption": "unite",
    "fourthOption": "squander",
    "correctOption": "squander",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "going around",
    "firstOption": "abroad",
    "secondOption": "bigamy",
    "thirdOption": "ban",
    "fourthOption": "roam",
    "correctOption": "abroad",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a runaway",
    "firstOption": "fugitive",
    "secondOption": "quarter",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "fiction",
    "correctOption": "fugitive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "serious trouble",
    "firstOption": "captive",
    "secondOption": "calamity",
    "thirdOption": "security",
    "fourthOption": "majority",
    "correctOption": "calamity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a very poor person",
    "firstOption": "vanish",
    "secondOption": "corpse",
    "thirdOption": "pauper",
    "fourthOption": "appeal",
    "correctOption": "pauper",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "jealousy",
    "firstOption": "envy",
    "secondOption": "hasty",
    "thirdOption": "theory",
    "fourthOption": "endure",
    "correctOption": "envy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a breakdown",
    "firstOption": "compete",
    "secondOption": "commence",
    "thirdOption": "gallant",
    "fourthOption": "collapse",
    "correctOption": "collapse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bring before a court",
    "firstOption": "related",
    "secondOption": "despite",
    "thirdOption": "probe",
    "fourthOption": "prosecute",
    "correctOption": "prosecute",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having two wives at the same",
    "firstOption": "scald",
    "secondOption": "bigamy",
    "thirdOption": "vague",
    "fourthOption": "rural",
    "correctOption": "bigamy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "able to be",
    "firstOption": "punish",
    "secondOption": "obstacle",
    "thirdOption": "partial",
    "fourthOption": "possible",
    "correctOption": "possible",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "force",
    "firstOption": "compel",
    "secondOption": "kneel",
    "thirdOption": "cease",
    "fourthOption": "logical",
    "correctOption": "compel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clumsy",
    "firstOption": "wad",
    "secondOption": "wary",
    "thirdOption": "awkward",
    "fourthOption": "weird",
    "correctOption": "awkward",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to expose to risk",
    "firstOption": "venture",
    "secondOption": "vessel",
    "thirdOption": "envy",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "venture",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "showing great respect",
    "firstOption": "flee",
    "secondOption": "awesome",
    "thirdOption": "menace",
    "fourthOption": "majestic",
    "correctOption": "awesome",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to manage",
    "firstOption": "guide",
    "secondOption": "wad",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "guide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "put an end to",
    "firstOption": "quench",
    "secondOption": "weird",
    "thirdOption": "envy",
    "fourthOption": "glance",
    "correctOption": "quench",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "be unfaithful",
    "firstOption": "betray",
    "secondOption": "witty",
    "thirdOption": "swarm",
    "fourthOption": "bulky",
    "correctOption": "betray",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "express",
    "firstOption": "data",
    "secondOption": "utter",
    "thirdOption": "untidy",
    "fourthOption": "mute",
    "correctOption": "utter",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make calm",
    "firstOption": "capacity",
    "secondOption": "prior",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "pacify",
    "correctOption": "pacify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "answer",
    "firstOption": "respond",
    "secondOption": "depict",
    "thirdOption": "pension",
    "fourthOption": "resume",
    "correctOption": "respond",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "gesture that directs in a particular direction",
    "firstOption": "legend",
    "secondOption": "beckon",
    "thirdOption": "verify",
    "fourthOption": "vacant",
    "correctOption": "beckon",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "in spite of",
    "firstOption": "merit",
    "secondOption": "dejected",
    "thirdOption": "devise",
    "fourthOption": "despite",
    "correctOption": "despite",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cause to break down",
    "firstOption": "insist",
    "secondOption": "disrupt",
    "thirdOption": "tyrant",
    "fourthOption": "migrate",
    "correctOption": "disrupt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "too hasty",
    "firstOption": "wrath",
    "secondOption": "brawl",
    "thirdOption": "hasty",
    "fourthOption": "rash",
    "correctOption": "rash",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very quick",
    "firstOption": "rapid",
    "secondOption": "rave",
    "thirdOption": "abide",
    "fourthOption": "humid",
    "correctOption": "rapid",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tire out",
    "firstOption": "expand",
    "secondOption": "exhaust",
    "thirdOption": "abuse",
    "fourthOption": "thrust",
    "correctOption": "exhaust",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "harshness",
    "firstOption": "detect",
    "secondOption": "capacity",
    "thirdOption": "severity",
    "fourthOption": "emerge",
    "correctOption": "severity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "weak",
    "firstOption": "pierce",
    "secondOption": "feeble",
    "thirdOption": "pledge",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "feeble",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "join together",
    "firstOption": "data",
    "secondOption": "unite",
    "thirdOption": "daze",
    "fourthOption": "unique",
    "correctOption": "unite",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stop",
    "firstOption": "wasp",
    "secondOption": "cease",
    "thirdOption": "elevate",
    "fourthOption": "aware",
    "correctOption": "cease",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "careful in spending",
    "firstOption": "obesity",
    "secondOption": "thrifty",
    "thirdOption": "crafty",
    "fourthOption": "ignite",
    "correctOption": "thrifty",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stingy",
    "firstOption": "wager",
    "secondOption": "miserly",
    "thirdOption": "magnify",
    "fourthOption": "novel",
    "correctOption": "miserly",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "king or queen",
    "firstOption": "monarch",
    "secondOption": "menace",
    "thirdOption": "aware",
    "fourthOption": "soar",
    "correctOption": "monarch",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "an exile",
    "firstOption": "oath",
    "secondOption": "urban",
    "thirdOption": "outlaw",
    "fourthOption": "novel",
    "correctOption": "outlaw",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "help to grow and develop",
    "firstOption": "corpse",
    "secondOption": "spouse",
    "thirdOption": "promote",
    "fourthOption": "proceed",
    "correctOption": "promote",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "getting less than the required food needed for health and growth",
    "firstOption": "underestimate",
    "secondOption": "promote",
    "thirdOption": "spouse",
    "fourthOption": "undernourished",
    "correctOption": "undernourished",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make clear or explain",
    "firstOption": "fortunate",
    "secondOption": "volunteer",
    "thirdOption": "distress",
    "fourthOption": "illustrate",
    "correctOption": "illustrate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "uncover",
    "firstOption": "disclose",
    "secondOption": "ignore",
    "thirdOption": "nimble",
    "fourthOption": "vicious",
    "correctOption": "disclose",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "too much",
    "firstOption": "expensive",
    "secondOption": "excessive",
    "thirdOption": "exhibit",
    "fourthOption": "excel",
    "correctOption": "excessive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a great misfortune",
    "firstOption": "aware",
    "secondOption": "disaster",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "cease",
    "correctOption": "disaster",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make change in",
    "firstOption": "pauper",
    "secondOption": "censor",
    "thirdOption": "utensil",
    "fourthOption": "endure",
    "correctOption": "censor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "offender",
    "firstOption": "calamity",
    "secondOption": "rapid",
    "thirdOption": "culprit",
    "fourthOption": "topic",
    "correctOption": "culprit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "young",
    "firstOption": "devise",
    "secondOption": "undeniable",
    "thirdOption": "juvenile",
    "fourthOption": "feminine",
    "correctOption": "juvenile",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "food used to attract fish",
    "firstOption": "vacant",
    "secondOption": "valid",
    "thirdOption": "bait",
    "fourthOption": "flee",
    "correctOption": "bait",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "keep firmly to some position",
    "firstOption": "revise",
    "secondOption": "merit",
    "thirdOption": "consent",
    "fourthOption": "insist",
    "correctOption": "insist",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hard work",
    "firstOption": "oral",
    "secondOption": "trifle",
    "thirdOption": "soar",
    "fourthOption": "toil",
    "correctOption": "toil",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stupid mistake",
    "firstOption": "brutal",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "blunder",
    "fourthOption": "squander",
    "correctOption": "blunder",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "confuse",
    "firstOption": "probe",
    "secondOption": "debate",
    "thirdOption": "verse",
    "fourthOption": "daze",
    "correctOption": "daze",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grieve",
    "firstOption": "doubt",
    "secondOption": "spouse",
    "thirdOption": "mourn",
    "fourthOption": "keen",
    "correctOption": "mourn",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grow less",
    "firstOption": "subside",
    "secondOption": "skim",
    "thirdOption": "abide",
    "fourthOption": "fragile",
    "correctOption": "subside",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make useless",
    "firstOption": "idle",
    "secondOption": "maim",
    "thirdOption": "valor",
    "fourthOption": "roam",
    "correctOption": "maim",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "understand",
    "firstOption": "conceal",
    "secondOption": "prominent",
    "thirdOption": "comprehend",
    "fourthOption": "tempest",
    "correctOption": "comprehend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "praise",
    "firstOption": "conclude",
    "secondOption": "descend",
    "thirdOption": "commend",
    "fourthOption": "torment",
    "correctOption": "commend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "coming last",
    "firstOption": "dwindle",
    "secondOption": "brutal",
    "thirdOption": "final",
    "fourthOption": "frank",
    "correctOption": "final",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make free from",
    "firstOption": "exempt",
    "secondOption": "reject",
    "thirdOption": "prompt",
    "fourthOption": "detect",
    "correctOption": "exempt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having too much pride",
    "firstOption": "wary",
    "secondOption": "warden",
    "thirdOption": "vain",
    "fourthOption": "verify",
    "correctOption": "vain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "act of saying or doing again",
    "firstOption": "repetition",
    "secondOption": "pedestrian",
    "thirdOption": "event",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "repetition",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "describe",
    "firstOption": "depict",
    "secondOption": "recent",
    "thirdOption": "jest",
    "fourthOption": "tact",
    "correctOption": "depict",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sure to die sometime",
    "firstOption": "shrill",
    "secondOption": "mortal",
    "thirdOption": "morgue",
    "fourthOption": "brutal",
    "correctOption": "mortal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "new",
    "firstOption": "novel",
    "secondOption": "topic",
    "thirdOption": "numb",
    "fourthOption": "soar",
    "correctOption": "novel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person in possession of a position",
    "firstOption": "document",
    "secondOption": "expand",
    "thirdOption": "occupant",
    "fourthOption": "client",
    "correctOption": "occupant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "decide on",
    "firstOption": "mount",
    "secondOption": "approach",
    "thirdOption": "opponent",
    "fourthOption": "appoint",
    "correctOption": "appoint",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "region",
    "firstOption": "quarter",
    "secondOption": "quote",
    "thirdOption": "swarm",
    "fourthOption": "refer",
    "correctOption": "quarter",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "place",
    "firstOption": "rave",
    "secondOption": "rage",
    "thirdOption": "abide",
    "fourthOption": "site",
    "correctOption": "site",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "repeat exactly the words",
    "firstOption": "outlaw",
    "secondOption": "quote",
    "thirdOption": "reform",
    "fourthOption": "tact",
    "correctOption": "quote",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a short division in bible",
    "firstOption": "weary",
    "secondOption": "morsel",
    "thirdOption": "excel",
    "fourthOption": "verse",
    "correctOption": "verse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the right or wrong of a action",
    "firstOption": "morality",
    "secondOption": "vocation",
    "thirdOption": "solitary",
    "fourthOption": "valid",
    "correctOption": "morality",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "wander",
    "firstOption": "rival",
    "secondOption": "oral",
    "thirdOption": "abroad",
    "fourthOption": "roam",
    "correctOption": "roam",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "draw to on self",
    "firstOption": "attract",
    "secondOption": "awkward",
    "thirdOption": "accurate",
    "fourthOption": "depict",
    "correctOption": "attract",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "one who travel regularly",
    "firstOption": "confine",
    "secondOption": "migrate",
    "thirdOption": "censor",
    "fourthOption": "commuter",
    "correctOption": "commuter",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "limit",
    "firstOption": "confine",
    "secondOption": "feminine",
    "thirdOption": "revise",
    "fourthOption": "torrent",
    "correctOption": "confine",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not busy",
    "firstOption": "idle",
    "secondOption": "unite",
    "thirdOption": "data",
    "fourthOption": "linger",
    "correctOption": "idle",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "image which is worshiped as a god",
    "firstOption": "head",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "wail",
    "fourthOption": "ignore",
    "correctOption": "idol",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "joke",
    "firstOption": "abuse",
    "secondOption": "sneer",
    "thirdOption": "jest",
    "fourthOption": "cease",
    "correctOption": "jest",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "loving one s country",
    "firstOption": "harmony",
    "secondOption": "avoid",
    "thirdOption": "narcotic",
    "fourthOption": "patriotic",
    "correctOption": "patriotic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disagree",
    "firstOption": "debate",
    "secondOption": "disclose",
    "thirdOption": "ignite",
    "fourthOption": "dispute",
    "correctOption": "dispute",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bravery",
    "firstOption": "valor",
    "secondOption": "verse",
    "thirdOption": "daze",
    "fourthOption": "vain",
    "correctOption": "valor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "crazy person",
    "firstOption": "lunatic",
    "secondOption": "finance",
    "thirdOption": "loyalty",
    "fourthOption": "valid",
    "correctOption": "lunatic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a blood vessel",
    "firstOption": "keen",
    "secondOption": "vision",
    "thirdOption": "peril",
    "fourthOption": "vein",
    "correctOption": "vein",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "without important happiness",
    "firstOption": "uneventful",
    "secondOption": "annual",
    "thirdOption": "essential",
    "fourthOption": "keen",
    "correctOption": "uneventful",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "producing much of anything",
    "firstOption": "fiction",
    "secondOption": "famine",
    "thirdOption": "shrill",
    "fourthOption": "fertile",
    "correctOption": "fertile",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hand over",
    "firstOption": "depart",
    "secondOption": "daze",
    "thirdOption": "reveal",
    "fourthOption": "refer",
    "correctOption": "refer",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "great pain",
    "firstOption": "descend",
    "secondOption": "disrupt",
    "thirdOption": "detest",
    "fourthOption": "distress",
    "correctOption": "distress",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make smaller in size",
    "firstOption": "diminish",
    "secondOption": "nominate",
    "thirdOption": "monarch",
    "fourthOption": "vicious",
    "correctOption": "diminish",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "greatest amount",
    "firstOption": "maximum",
    "secondOption": "vague",
    "thirdOption": "amateur",
    "fourthOption": "cancel",
    "correctOption": "maximum",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go quickly",
    "firstOption": "flee",
    "secondOption": "redeem",
    "thirdOption": "cease",
    "fourthOption": "heir",
    "correctOption": "flee",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "open to attack",
    "firstOption": "illegal",
    "secondOption": "vulnerable",
    "thirdOption": "survive",
    "fourthOption": "obstacle",
    "correctOption": "vulnerable",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "mean",
    "firstOption": "verify",
    "secondOption": "signify",
    "thirdOption": "charity",
    "fourthOption": "vicinity",
    "correctOption": "signify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stories that attempt to explain something in nature",
    "firstOption": "minority",
    "secondOption": "gloomy",
    "thirdOption": "mythology",
    "fourthOption": "authority",
    "correctOption": "mythology",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "associate",
    "firstOption": "collapse",
    "secondOption": "colleague",
    "thirdOption": "collide",
    "fourthOption": "vague",
    "correctOption": "colleague",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cause very great pain to",
    "firstOption": "torrent",
    "secondOption": "torment",
    "thirdOption": "tragedy",
    "fourthOption": "commence",
    "correctOption": "torment",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to supply",
    "firstOption": "ponder",
    "secondOption": "abide",
    "thirdOption": "provide",
    "fourthOption": "avoid",
    "correctOption": "provide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "faithfulness",
    "firstOption": "depart",
    "secondOption": "loyalty",
    "thirdOption": "qualify",
    "fourthOption": "compete",
    "correctOption": "loyalty",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who offer one s service",
    "firstOption": "unite",
    "secondOption": "pauper",
    "thirdOption": "volunteer",
    "fourthOption": "mount",
    "correctOption": "volunteer",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to harm or injure",
    "firstOption": "provide",
    "secondOption": "expose",
    "thirdOption": "adequate",
    "fourthOption": "prejudice",
    "correctOption": "prejudice",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having a high pitch",
    "firstOption": "parole",
    "secondOption": "scowl",
    "thirdOption": "toil",
    "fourthOption": "shrill",
    "correctOption": "shrill",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "full of fun",
    "firstOption": "mount",
    "secondOption": "topic",
    "thirdOption": "jolly",
    "fourthOption": "heed",
    "correctOption": "jolly",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cleverly amusing",
    "firstOption": "untidy",
    "secondOption": "hazy",
    "thirdOption": "rival",
    "fourthOption": "witty",
    "correctOption": "witty",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hold back",
    "firstOption": "sneer",
    "secondOption": "abide",
    "thirdOption": "kneel",
    "fourthOption": "hinder",
    "correctOption": "hinder",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "speech",
    "firstOption": "lecture",
    "secondOption": "detest",
    "thirdOption": "debate",
    "fourthOption": "fiction",
    "correctOption": "lecture",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make bad use",
    "firstOption": "abuse",
    "secondOption": "awesome",
    "thirdOption": "guide",
    "fourthOption": "spouse",
    "correctOption": "abuse",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "speak indistinctly",
    "firstOption": "source",
    "secondOption": "summit",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "mumble",
    "correctOption": "mumble",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "silent",
    "firstOption": "mute",
    "secondOption": "wasp",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "abuse",
    "correctOption": "mute",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "smell",
    "firstOption": "oath",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "wad",
    "fourthOption": "lack",
    "correctOption": "wad",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "keep",
    "firstOption": "merit",
    "secondOption": "peril",
    "thirdOption": "retain",
    "fourthOption": "rash",
    "correctOption": "retain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who is proposed for office",
    "firstOption": "candidate",
    "secondOption": "hesitate",
    "thirdOption": "ventilate",
    "fourthOption": "manipulate",
    "correctOption": "candidate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go before",
    "firstOption": "resent",
    "secondOption": "precede",
    "thirdOption": "debate",
    "fourthOption": "perish",
    "correctOption": "precede",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "growing up to manhood",
    "firstOption": "adolescent",
    "secondOption": "collide",
    "thirdOption": "complacent",
    "fourthOption": "torrent",
    "correctOption": "adolescent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "educating both sexes",
    "firstOption": "coeducational",
    "secondOption": "postpone",
    "thirdOption": "potential",
    "fourthOption": "stationary",
    "correctOption": "coeducational",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fundamental",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "rival",
    "thirdOption": "appeal",
    "fourthOption": "radical",
    "correctOption": "radical",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "natural",
    "firstOption": "fortunate",
    "secondOption": "contagious",
    "thirdOption": "misfortune",
    "fourthOption": "spontaneous",
    "correctOption": "spontaneous",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remove from the top",
    "firstOption": "ban",
    "secondOption": "rapid",
    "thirdOption": "skim",
    "fourthOption": "daze",
    "correctOption": "skim",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "render unsusceptible to a disease by inoculating",
    "firstOption": "valiant",
    "secondOption": "vague",
    "thirdOption": "deceive",
    "fourthOption": "vaccinate",
    "correctOption": "vaccinate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disorderly",
    "firstOption": "vaccinate",
    "secondOption": "deceive",
    "thirdOption": "valiant",
    "fourthOption": "untidy",
    "correctOption": "untidy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "too used for practical purpose",
    "firstOption": "utensil",
    "secondOption": "insist",
    "thirdOption": "excel",
    "fourthOption": "quench",
    "correctOption": "utensil",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "easily affected",
    "firstOption": "site",
    "secondOption": "negative",
    "thirdOption": "sensitive",
    "fourthOption": "lecture",
    "correctOption": "sensitive",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "moderate",
    "firstOption": "temperate",
    "secondOption": "merit",
    "thirdOption": "parole",
    "fourthOption": "lecture",
    "correctOption": "temperate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not clear",
    "firstOption": "endure",
    "secondOption": "data",
    "thirdOption": "vigor",
    "fourthOption": "vague",
    "correctOption": "vague",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "raise",
    "firstOption": "talent",
    "secondOption": "blend",
    "thirdOption": "embrace",
    "fourthOption": "elevate",
    "correctOption": "elevate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "something whose outcome is determined by chance",
    "firstOption": "lottery",
    "secondOption": "witty",
    "thirdOption": "ponder",
    "fourthOption": "torrent",
    "correctOption": "lottery",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "money matters",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "miniature",
    "thirdOption": "finance",
    "fourthOption": "feminine",
    "correctOption": "finance",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "get",
    "firstOption": "obtain",
    "secondOption": "ban",
    "thirdOption": "final",
    "fourthOption": "mature",
    "correctOption": "obtain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "moving picture",
    "firstOption": "dismal",
    "secondOption": "client",
    "thirdOption": "final",
    "fourthOption": "cinema",
    "correctOption": "cinema",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "happening",
    "firstOption": "plea",
    "secondOption": "event",
    "thirdOption": "recent",
    "fourthOption": "reveal",
    "correctOption": "event",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "throw aside",
    "firstOption": "decade",
    "secondOption": "vacant",
    "thirdOption": "placard",
    "fourthOption": "discard",
    "correctOption": "discard",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "aspire",
    "firstOption": "sneer",
    "secondOption": "soar",
    "thirdOption": "probe",
    "fourthOption": "preserve",
    "correctOption": "soar",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "later",
    "firstOption": "defect",
    "secondOption": "neglect",
    "thirdOption": "subsequent",
    "fourthOption": "observant",
    "correctOption": "subsequent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tell",
    "firstOption": "dejected",
    "secondOption": "rage",
    "thirdOption": "tempt",
    "fourthOption": "relate",
    "correctOption": "relate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not moving",
    "firstOption": "symbol",
    "secondOption": "stationary",
    "thirdOption": "nominate",
    "fourthOption": "approach",
    "correctOption": "stationary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quick",
    "firstOption": "compel",
    "secondOption": "prompt",
    "thirdOption": "drench",
    "fourthOption": "compete",
    "correctOption": "prompt",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quick",
    "firstOption": "rage",
    "secondOption": "wad",
    "thirdOption": "hasty",
    "fourthOption": "wasp",
    "correctOption": "hasty",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "burn slightly",
    "firstOption": "reform",
    "secondOption": "scarce",
    "thirdOption": "shriek",
    "fourthOption": "scorch",
    "correctOption": "scorch",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a violent distribution",
    "firstOption": "prompt",
    "secondOption": "expand",
    "thirdOption": "tempest",
    "fourthOption": "merit",
    "correctOption": "tempest",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "calm",
    "firstOption": "opt",
    "secondOption": "soothe",
    "thirdOption": "quota",
    "fourthOption": "promote",
    "correctOption": "soothe",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having kind feeling toward others",
    "firstOption": "sympathetic",
    "secondOption": "panic",
    "thirdOption": "summit",
    "fourthOption": "compete",
    "correctOption": "sympathetic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "buy back",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "reform",
    "thirdOption": "redeem",
    "fourthOption": "dilemma",
    "correctOption": "redeem",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "begin again",
    "firstOption": "precede",
    "secondOption": "vague",
    "thirdOption": "resume",
    "fourthOption": "rage",
    "correctOption": "resume",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "going well together",
    "firstOption": "torment",
    "secondOption": "harmony",
    "thirdOption": "enormous",
    "fourthOption": "urban",
    "correctOption": "harmony",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hold back",
    "firstOption": "refrain",
    "secondOption": "refer",
    "thirdOption": "recline",
    "fourthOption": "cease",
    "correctOption": "refrain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not lawful",
    "firstOption": "partial",
    "secondOption": "illegal",
    "thirdOption": "villain",
    "fourthOption": "novel",
    "correctOption": "illegal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "drug",
    "firstOption": "vain",
    "secondOption": "narcotic",
    "thirdOption": "traitor",
    "fourthOption": "prior",
    "correctOption": "narcotic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who inherit any thing",
    "firstOption": "heir",
    "secondOption": "heed",
    "thirdOption": "hazy",
    "fourthOption": "jest",
    "correctOption": "heir",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "kingly",
    "firstOption": "mount",
    "secondOption": "maximum",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "majestic",
    "correctOption": "majestic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "become smaller",
    "firstOption": "idle",
    "secondOption": "ignore",
    "thirdOption": "dwindle",
    "fourthOption": "blend",
    "correctOption": "dwindle",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "extra",
    "firstOption": "rural",
    "secondOption": "campus",
    "thirdOption": "surpass",
    "fourthOption": "surplus",
    "correctOption": "surplus",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who betray",
    "firstOption": "heir",
    "secondOption": "tempt",
    "thirdOption": "thrust",
    "fourthOption": "traitor",
    "correctOption": "traitor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "consider carefully",
    "firstOption": "vaccinate",
    "secondOption": "defraud",
    "thirdOption": "dejected",
    "fourthOption": "deliberate",
    "correctOption": "deliberate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who destroy",
    "firstOption": "vandal",
    "secondOption": "oral",
    "thirdOption": "radical",
    "fourthOption": "annual",
    "correctOption": "vandal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lack of rain",
    "firstOption": "prosper",
    "secondOption": "drought",
    "thirdOption": "spouse",
    "fourthOption": "tumult",
    "correctOption": "drought",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remain faithful",
    "firstOption": "abide",
    "secondOption": "abroad",
    "thirdOption": "warden",
    "fourthOption": "abuse",
    "correctOption": "abide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unite",
    "firstOption": "refer",
    "secondOption": "unify",
    "thirdOption": "linger",
    "fourthOption": "insist",
    "correctOption": "unify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "peak",
    "firstOption": "skim",
    "secondOption": "symbol",
    "thirdOption": "summit",
    "fourthOption": "numb",
    "correctOption": "summit",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "give careful attention",
    "firstOption": "abide",
    "secondOption": "humid",
    "thirdOption": "flee",
    "fourthOption": "heed",
    "correctOption": "heed",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "account of a person s life written by another person",
    "firstOption": "uneasy",
    "secondOption": "biography",
    "thirdOption": "collapse",
    "fourthOption": "oath",
    "correctOption": "biography",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "soak",
    "firstOption": "drench",
    "secondOption": "defect",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "blend",
    "correctOption": "drench",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "crowd number",
    "firstOption": "swarm",
    "secondOption": "heir",
    "thirdOption": "maim",
    "fourthOption": "source",
    "correctOption": "swarm",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "move unsteadily side to side",
    "firstOption": "parole",
    "secondOption": "forbid",
    "thirdOption": "wobble",
    "fourthOption": "possible",
    "correctOption": "wobble",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "noise",
    "firstOption": "torment",
    "secondOption": "unruly",
    "thirdOption": "nimble",
    "fourthOption": "tumult",
    "correctOption": "tumult",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go down on one s knee",
    "firstOption": "final",
    "secondOption": "kneel",
    "thirdOption": "flee",
    "fourthOption": "appeal",
    "correctOption": "kneel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sad",
    "firstOption": "tempest",
    "secondOption": "dejected",
    "thirdOption": "event",
    "fourthOption": "majestic",
    "correctOption": "dejected",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "willing to obey",
    "firstOption": "opponent",
    "secondOption": "frequent",
    "thirdOption": "obedient",
    "fourthOption": "predict",
    "correctOption": "obedient",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go back",
    "firstOption": "flee",
    "secondOption": "recede",
    "thirdOption": "redeem",
    "fourthOption": "rarely",
    "correctOption": "recede",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "absolute ruler",
    "firstOption": "tyrant",
    "secondOption": "depart",
    "thirdOption": "torment",
    "fourthOption": "threat",
    "correctOption": "tyrant",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "generous giving to the poor",
    "firstOption": "aware",
    "secondOption": "charity",
    "thirdOption": "morality",
    "fourthOption": "weary",
    "correctOption": "charity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "decision of a jury",
    "firstOption": "vision",
    "secondOption": "horrid",
    "thirdOption": "verdict",
    "fourthOption": "obedient",
    "correctOption": "verdict",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "discover",
    "firstOption": "unearth",
    "secondOption": "merit",
    "thirdOption": "abundant",
    "fourthOption": "hasty",
    "correctOption": "unearth",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "go away",
    "firstOption": "depict",
    "secondOption": "devise",
    "thirdOption": "unearth",
    "fourthOption": "depart",
    "correctOption": "depart",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "agree",
    "firstOption": "dwindle",
    "secondOption": "guide",
    "thirdOption": "coincide",
    "fourthOption": "conclude",
    "correctOption": "coincide",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "call off",
    "firstOption": "cancel",
    "secondOption": "daze",
    "thirdOption": "pauper",
    "fourthOption": "excel",
    "correctOption": "cancel",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "person who owes something",
    "firstOption": "depict",
    "secondOption": "vigor",
    "thirdOption": "venture",
    "fourthOption": "debtor",
    "correctOption": "debtor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "able to be read",
    "firstOption": "peril",
    "secondOption": "mumble",
    "thirdOption": "legible",
    "fourthOption": "revive",
    "correctOption": "legible",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "poster",
    "firstOption": "sacred",
    "secondOption": "plea",
    "thirdOption": "placard",
    "fourthOption": "pledge",
    "correctOption": "placard",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "spreading by contact",
    "firstOption": "spontaneous",
    "secondOption": "consider",
    "thirdOption": "contagious",
    "fourthOption": "obvious",
    "correctOption": "contagious",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "persons prepare for religious work",
    "firstOption": "clergy",
    "secondOption": "flee",
    "thirdOption": "theory",
    "fourthOption": "plea",
    "correctOption": "clergy",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "usual",
    "firstOption": "customary",
    "secondOption": "lottery",
    "thirdOption": "hasty",
    "fourthOption": "lubricate",
    "correctOption": "customary",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clear",
    "firstOption": "transparent",
    "secondOption": "frequent",
    "thirdOption": "torment",
    "fourthOption": "subsequent",
    "correctOption": "transparent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "pour boiling liquid over",
    "firstOption": "tact",
    "secondOption": "casual",
    "thirdOption": "scald",
    "fourthOption": "discard",
    "correctOption": "scald",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "widespread",
    "firstOption": "abide",
    "secondOption": "epidemic",
    "thirdOption": "miserly",
    "fourthOption": "economical",
    "correctOption": "epidemic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "extreme fatness",
    "firstOption": "obesity",
    "secondOption": "obedient",
    "thirdOption": "heir",
    "fourthOption": "massive",
    "correctOption": "obesity",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "make too much of",
    "firstOption": "wager",
    "secondOption": "magnify",
    "thirdOption": "partial",
    "fourthOption": "maintain",
    "correctOption": "magnify",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "herapeutic treatment of disease through the manipulation of the spinal column",
    "firstOption": "appropriate",
    "secondOption": "authority",
    "thirdOption": "wrath",
    "fourthOption": "chiropractor",
    "correctOption": "chiropractor",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "obstruction",
    "firstOption": "mortal",
    "secondOption": "obtain",
    "thirdOption": "obstacle",
    "fourthOption": "oral",
    "correctOption": "obstacle",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "change the air in",
    "firstOption": "venture",
    "secondOption": "ventilate",
    "thirdOption": "justice",
    "fourthOption": "adequate",
    "correctOption": "ventilate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "endanger",
    "firstOption": "persuade",
    "secondOption": "jeopardize",
    "thirdOption": "recline",
    "fourthOption": "survive",
    "correctOption": "jeopardize",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "saying no",
    "firstOption": "penalize",
    "secondOption": "negative",
    "thirdOption": "venture",
    "fourthOption": "legible",
    "correctOption": "negative",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "financial benefit paid after a person has stopped working",
    "firstOption": "utensil",
    "secondOption": "pension",
    "thirdOption": "persist",
    "fourthOption": "vein",
    "correctOption": "pension",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lively",
    "firstOption": "roam",
    "secondOption": "gallant",
    "thirdOption": "alter",
    "fourthOption": "vital",
    "correctOption": "vital",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "of a city",
    "firstOption": "uneasy",
    "secondOption": "final",
    "thirdOption": "municipal",
    "fourthOption": "menace",
    "correctOption": "municipal",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "spoken",
    "firstOption": "wrath",
    "secondOption": "scald",
    "thirdOption": "mount",
    "fourthOption": "oral",
    "correctOption": "oral",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "self-satisfied",
    "firstOption": "menace",
    "secondOption": "prominent",
    "thirdOption": "employee",
    "fourthOption": "complacent",
    "correctOption": "complacent",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bee",
    "firstOption": "jest",
    "secondOption": "wad",
    "thirdOption": "rage",
    "fourthOption": "wasp",
    "correctOption": "wasp",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "restore to good condition",
    "firstOption": "morality",
    "secondOption": "relieve",
    "thirdOption": "rehabilitate",
    "fourthOption": "repetition",
    "correctOption": "rehabilitate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "conditional freedom",
    "firstOption": "parole",
    "secondOption": "verse",
    "thirdOption": "rural",
    "fourthOption": "baffle",
    "correctOption": "parole",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not horizontal",
    "firstOption": "vertical",
    "secondOption": "verse",
    "thirdOption": "verify",
    "fourthOption": "peril",
    "correctOption": "vertical",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a great number",
    "firstOption": "elevate",
    "secondOption": "merit",
    "thirdOption": "glimpse",
    "fourthOption": "multitude",
    "correctOption": "multitude",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "appoint an office",
    "firstOption": "daze",
    "secondOption": "threat",
    "thirdOption": "morality",
    "fourthOption": "nominate",
    "correctOption": "nominate",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "capability",
    "firstOption": "client",
    "secondOption": "potential",
    "thirdOption": "opponent",
    "fourthOption": "brutal",
    "correctOption": "potential",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "place where corpses are stored before post-mortem exam or before being claimed for burial, mortuary",
    "firstOption": "morgue",
    "secondOption": "rage",
    "thirdOption": "fragile",
    "fourthOption": "mumble",
    "correctOption": "morgue",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "took up all the attention",
    "firstOption": "preoccupied",
    "secondOption": "expand",
    "thirdOption": "prohibit",
    "fourthOption": "prejudice",
    "correctOption": "preoccupied",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "covering for furniture",
    "firstOption": "quote",
    "secondOption": "upholstery",
    "thirdOption": "charity",
    "fourthOption": "spouse",
    "correctOption": "upholstery",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "lack of interest",
    "firstOption": "underdog",
    "secondOption": "miniature",
    "thirdOption": "distress",
    "fourthOption": "indifference",
    "correctOption": "indifference",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "keep",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "dismal",
    "thirdOption": "vaccinate",
    "fourthOption": "maintain",
    "correctOption": "maintain",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "treat coldly",
    "firstOption": "snub",
    "secondOption": "envy",
    "thirdOption": "wasp",
    "fourthOption": "opt",
    "correctOption": "snub",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stand",
    "firstOption": "wad",
    "secondOption": "rave",
    "thirdOption": "endure",
    "fourthOption": "penalize",
    "correctOption": "endure",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very great anger",
    "firstOption": "rave",
    "secondOption": "frank",
    "thirdOption": "wrath",
    "fourthOption": "wasp",
    "correctOption": "wrath",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "uncover",
    "firstOption": "employee",
    "secondOption": "evidence",
    "thirdOption": "cease",
    "fourthOption": "expose",
    "correctOption": "expose",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "story coming from the past",
    "firstOption": "logical",
    "secondOption": "defect",
    "thirdOption": "talent",
    "fourthOption": "legend",
    "correctOption": "legend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "consider carefully",
    "firstOption": "ponder",
    "secondOption": "slender",
    "thirdOption": "vandal",
    "fourthOption": "roam",
    "correctOption": "ponder",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "submit",
    "firstOption": "rash",
    "secondOption": "defiant",
    "thirdOption": "resign",
    "fourthOption": "refer",
    "correctOption": "resign",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "intense",
    "firstOption": "resign",
    "secondOption": "legend",
    "thirdOption": "rash",
    "fourthOption": "drastic",
    "correctOption": "drastic",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "place where boats can be be tied up and load or unload cargo",
    "firstOption": "amend",
    "secondOption": "drastic",
    "thirdOption": "ballot",
    "fourthOption": "wharf",
    "correctOption": "wharf",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "improve",
    "firstOption": "talent",
    "secondOption": "faithful",
    "thirdOption": "ballot",
    "fourthOption": "amend",
    "correctOption": "amend",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "slip of paper on which a vote is written",
    "firstOption": "narcotic",
    "secondOption": "baggage",
    "thirdOption": "baffle",
    "fourthOption": "ballot",
    "correctOption": "ballot",
    "category": "504_english_to_english"
  }
]
